<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Andrii Bilorus</title>
    <link>http://andrii.bilor.us/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Andrii Bilorus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://andrii.bilor.us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The short story about my OpenSUSE installation</title>
      <link>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/opensuse_installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/opensuse_installation/</guid>
      <description>Installation I love OpenSUSE, I used it when its version was 9. I remember the beautiful KDE, perfectly working YaST. Or maybe I am just old enough so that all those things seem nice to me.
Long story short after long period of using fedora/ubuntu I decided to find out how good OpenSUSE is. I took my Intel NUC, put the flash drive with dowloaded image in it, and pressed power button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create VM in QEMU/KVM environment</title>
      <link>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/install_kvm_vm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/install_kvm_vm/</guid>
      <description>Here I am going to create a VM. Since I&amp;rsquo;ve never tried CentOS 5, I decided to give it a shot. It has the old good sysv init system, it&amp;rsquo;s old, not obsolete. By this examle I will show you how to create and manage QEMU/KVM virtual machine without GUI utilities. First of all create a virtual disk of the desired size. Here for example, we will create a 20 GB disk with the raw disk format: You can also try to use qcow2 format which gives you some additional benefits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enable wireless network on Intel NUC running Fedora Linux</title>
      <link>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/enable_wireless_network_on_intel_nuc_running_fedora/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/enable_wireless_network_on_intel_nuc_running_fedora/</guid>
      <description>I am a happy owner of Inetl NUC computer. Recently I installed Fedora on it (right after I tested it as a VM). It was minimal installation. After I had logged in, I noticed that wireless network interface was unavailable. Quite wierd, taking into account that it worked fine during the installation process.
I looked around, device was connected:
# lspci ... 3a:00.0 Network controller: Intel Corporation Wireless 8265 / 8275 (rev 78) .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My journey with Fedora. The begining.</title>
      <link>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/my_journey_with_fedora/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrii.bilor.us/notes/my_journey_with_fedora/</guid>
      <description>Let me start with saying that I have been an ubuntu guy. Back in 2008 I met ubuntu first time, since than I have used different linux operating systems. In 2014 I switched to deb-based distros on my desktop. For some reason every time I tried redhat-like OS, the venture failed. Every time some crap happened. In addition, I don’t really like neither the current fedora artwork nor its fonts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://andrii.bilor.us/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://andrii.bilor.us/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Andrii Bilorus. You can call me Andrew or whatever you want.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>